Now that you've created a KAT can workspace and added the simple arm package to it,
ここでは作成したCatkinが作業領域になり、sample_armパッケージを作業領域に追加します
you're ready to write some Ross nodes.
ROS ノードを記述する準備ができました
In this lesson, you'll be writing notes in Python that publish and subscribe to topics.
このレッスンでは トピック(領域)を作成して、非同期にメッセージを送信する Python でメモを記述します
And you'll write a Ross service that can be called
また ほかのノードまたはコマンドラインから呼び出せる
from other nodes or from the command line.
Ross サービスを記述します
The first node that you'll be writing is called simple mover.
記述する最初のノードは simple mover といいます
The simple mover node does nothing more than publish joint angle commands to simple arm.
simple mover ノードは ジョイント角コマンドを simple arm にパブリッシュするだけのノードです
After you've developed a basic understanding of the general structure of a Ross node,
Rossノードの一般的な構造の基本がわかると
you'll be writing another node called arm mover.
arm mover という別のノードを記述します
The arm mover node provides a service called safe move,
arm mover ノードは safe move と呼ばれるサービスを提供します
which allows the arm to be moved to any position
これは 「安全」と見なされたワークスペース内の
within its workspace which has been deemed to be safe.
任意の位置にアームを移動できます
The safe zone is bounded by
安全ゾーンは最小ジョイント角と最大ジョイント角で
minimum and maximum joint angles and it's configurable via the Ross parameter server.
境界をつけ Ross パラメーターサーバーから設定できます
The last node you'll write in this lesson, is the look away node.
このレッスンで記述する最後のノードは look away ノードです
This node subscribes to a topic where camera data is being published.
このノードは カメラ データのパブリッシュ先であるトピックにサブスクライブします
When the camera detects an image with uniform color,
カメラが同一色の画像を検出すると
meaning that it's looking at the sky,
(カメラが空を向いている場合)
the node will call the safe move service to move the arm to a new position.
ノードは safe move サービスを呼び出してアームを新しい位置に移動します
With these new skills, you'll have everything you need to
これらの新しいスキルで このプログラムの次のプロジェクトに取り組むために必要なことが
tackle the upcoming projects in this program.
すべて身に付きます